<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Richard Acquah-Sarpong</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Richard Acquah-Sarpong</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leschewski, A., Aragon, M. C., Weatherspoon, D., Barale, K., Auld, G., **Acquah-Sarpong, R.**, &amp; Baker, S. S</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/authors/leschewski-a.-aragon-m.-c.-weatherspoon-d.-barale-k.-auld-g.-acquah-sarpong-r.--baker-s.-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/authors/leschewski-a.-aragon-m.-c.-weatherspoon-d.-barale-k.-auld-g.-acquah-sarpong-r.--baker-s.-s/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leschewski, A., Aragon, M. C., Weatherspoon, D., Barale, K., Auld, G., Acquah-Sarpong, R., &amp; Baker, S. S</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/authors/leschewski-a.-aragon-m.-c.-weatherspoon-d.-barale-k.-auld-g.-acquah-sarpong-r.--baker-s.-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/authors/leschewski-a.-aragon-m.-c.-weatherspoon-d.-barale-k.-auld-g.-acquah-sarpong-r.--baker-s.-s/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am PhD Candidate in Applied Economics, with a specialization in Regional and Environmental Economics. My research focuses on the intersection of regional policies, environmental factors, and how they influence business decisions within spatial and geographic contexts. I am particularly interested in investigating the mechanisms through which place-based policies, such as minimum wage laws, and environmental policies or events shape the spatial distribution of economic activities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my current research, I explore how economic policies and environmental conditions affect firm behavior, investment decisions, and regional economic resilience. My current work explores the impact of Oregon’s three-tier minimum wage system on the rural-urban development divide, with a focus on firm survival and economic stability. This research aims to provide insights into how differentiated wage policies in distinct geographic regions can either mitigate or exacerbate economic disparities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
